Guide to the David Skorton papers, 2006-2015.
Skorton, David papers
- Miscellany Projects, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Commencement Weekend, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 45)
- Cornell Alumni Magazine, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Reunion-Olin Lecture, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Reunion-Oldest Classes Reception, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 48)
- Reunion Classes of 1983, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 49)
- Reunion Classes of 1988, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 50)
- Reunion Classes of 1963, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Reunion Classes of 1948, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 52)
- Reunion Classes of 1958, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 53)
- Reunion Classes of 1953, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 54)
- Reunion Classes of 1973, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 55)
- Veterinary Medicine Reception, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 56)
- State of the Univesity Address, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 57)
- System for Tracking Administrative Reports Celebration, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 58)
- Service Recognition Dinner, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 59)
- Cornell Retirees Association Lunch, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 60)
- New Trustee Dinner, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 61)
- Watt Webb 80th Birthday Symposium, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 62)
- Business of Higher Education Financing Globalization, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 63)
- Tanner Dinner, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 64)
- Miscellany Projects, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 65)
- International Development Conference, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 66)
- Baily Plaza, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 67)
- Meeting of the Minds, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 68)
- Robert Richardson Symposium, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 69)
- Scholarship Event at Susan Lynch Home, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 70)
- Sage Chapel Service, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 71)
- Staff Commencement Recognition, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 72)
- Jack Blakely Reunion Symposium, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 73)
- Cornell Council Administrative Board Meeting, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 74)
- Ad Hoc Budget Group, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 75)
- Assembly-Employee, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 76)
- Assembly-Graduate and Professional Student, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 77)
- Assembly-Student, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 78)
- Assembly-University, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 79)
- Collaborative Work Group I, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 80)
- Collaborative Work Group I, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 81)
- Collaborative Work Group II, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 82)
- Education City, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Education City, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Budget and Reserve Adjustments, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Senior Leadership Meetings, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Senior Staff - August, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Senior Staff - September, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Senior Staff - September, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Senior Staff - October, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Senior Staff - November, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Senior Staff - December, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Senior Staff - January, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Senior Staff - February, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Senior Staff - March, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Senior Staff - April, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Senior Staff - May, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Senior Staff - June, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Senior Staff - July, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Senior Staff Budget Reduction Scenarios, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Strategic Planning, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Strategic Planning, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Cornell Zone: Photographic Mediation, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Theoretical and Applied Mechanics, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Weiss Presidential Fellows, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Annual Fund Letter, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Swanson Dedication, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Cornell Alumni Magazine, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Miscellany Projects, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Physics Graduate Students, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- New Student Convocation, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Tapestry of Possibilities, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Graduate Student Orientation, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Community Welcome Back Letters, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Cornell Daily Sun, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Community Event for Biddy Martin, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Dinner for Biddy Martin, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Reunion Kick-Off, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Cornell Population Program, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Asian/American Student Association, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Gettysburg the Power of Words, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Presidential Councillor Dinner and Annual Meeting, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- World Food Bank, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Carolyn Ainslie Reception, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Miller Division of Student Services Dedication Ceremony, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- Foreign Affairs Article, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Foreign Affairs Article, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- Sage Chapel Program, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Faculty Senate, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Lord God Bird Dinner, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Homecoming Native American Festival, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Atkinson Dinner Toast, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Myra Hart Foremost Benefactor, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Risk Management Celebration, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- R. Morgan Literary Lunch, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Keeton House Opening, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Real Estate Conference, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Frank Rhodes Exemplary Alumni Service Award, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Business Advance Course, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Tisch University Professor Lunch, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Weiss/Lynch Visit, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Cornell Daily Sun, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Cornell Alumni Magazine, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Jacobs Scholar Dinner, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- AARP Award, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Cornell University Finance and Administration, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- International Astronomy Conference, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Helene Viramontes Literary Lunch, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Child Care Center Ribbon Cutting, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Faculty Panel on Life Sciences, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Weill Dinner, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Weill Hall Dedication, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Lubna Olyan Introduction, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- State of the University Address, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Scholarship Dinner, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Annual Fund Breakfast, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Cleveland Cornell Club 100th Anniversary, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Cornell Women's Club of Cortland County, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Seattle All-Alumni, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Microsoft Lunch, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- CHE, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Cornell Daily Sun, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Tom Shires Memorial Event, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Into the Streets, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Parents Weekend, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Staff Open Forum, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Diversity Forum, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 40)
- Cornell Adult University Trip, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 41)
- Miscellany Projects - Sept., Oct., 2008 (Box 8, Folder 42)
- Cornell Chaplains, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 43)
- Appel Fellows Dinner, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 44)
- Wason Collection, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 45)
- Local Leaders Brunch, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 46)
- Judy Biggs Foremost Benefactor, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 47)
- Assemblies Leadership Breakfast, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 48)
- Carin Ruff Literary Lunch, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 49)
- Edutopia, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 50)
- 400 Club Breakfast, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 51)
- Miscellany Projects - November, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 52)
- Don Opatrny Foremost Benefactor, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 53)
- Biomedical Engineering 411 Lecture, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 54)
- Cornell Alumni Magazine, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 55)
- Iran Background for India Trip, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 56)
- Mumbai Vigils, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 57)
- India Conference, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 58)
- Mumbai All-Alumni, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 59)
- January Graduates Ceremony, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 60)
- Year-end Financial Message, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 61)
- Miscellany Projects - December, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 62)
- President's Circle Dinner, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 63)
- Cornell Football Association, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 64)
- Budget Powerpoint, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 65)
- Iowa City Chamber, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 66)
- Cornell Daily Sun, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 67)
- Miscellany Projects - January, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 68)
- Cornell Alumni Magazine, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 69)
- Weiss Presidential Fellows, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 70)
- Cornell Association of Class Officers Mid-Winter Meeting, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 71)
- Business Higher Education Forum Conference, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 72)
- ILR Colloquium, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 73)
- Senior Class Campaign Reception, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 74)
- VanClief Stefanson Literary Lunch, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 75)
- Harris Dinner, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 76)
- Cornell Group Dinner, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 77)
- Appel Dinner Councillors, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 78)
- Investment Committee, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 79)
- Rosenberg Dinner, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 80)
- Miscellany Projects - February, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 81)
- President's Council of Cornell Women, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 82)
- Distinguished Chair Holders with Trustees, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 83)
- Community Financial Message, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 84)
- International Women's Day, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 85)
- Cornell Daily Sun, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 86)
- California Dinner, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 87)
- Cornell Silicon Valley 10, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 88)
- Computing and Information Science Advisor Board Meeting, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 89)
- Miller Dinner, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 90)
- Snow Lecture at Weill Cornell Medical College, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 91)
- Becker House - Research Ethics, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 92)
- Melissa Bank Literary Lunch, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 93)
- Commencement Greetings, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 94)
- 400 Club Breakfast, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 95)
- Cornell Alumni Magazine Article, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 96)
- Service Awards Dinner, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 97)
- Hatfield Lecture, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 98)
- Cornell in the Capital, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 99)
- Arts and Sciences Advisory Council, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 100)
- Middle States Accreditation, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  Correspondence
- Campus Code of Conduct, 2007-2008 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Ad Hoc Committee on Sustainable Endowment, 2007-2008 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Assistant Judicial Administrator Request, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Association of Public and Land Grant Universities (APLU) Africana Initiative - Gates Foundation, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Senate Finance Committee, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Association of Public and Land Grant Universities (APLU) Africana Initiative - Kitchen Cabinet, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Association of Public and Land Grant Universities (APLU) Africana Initiative - Meeting Materials, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  Meeting materials
- Association of Public and Land Grant Universities (APLU) Africana Initiative - Press, 2008-2009 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  Correspondence/Articles
- Campus Master Plan, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Ratan Tata, 2009 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Reimagining Cornell - Kick off, 2009 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- 2009 Weiss Presidential Fellows, 2009 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Ivy and Sustainability Workgroup, 2009-04-07 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Chinese Fungi Homecoming, 2009-04-13 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Perkins Prize, 2009-04-15 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Amartya Senator Lecture, 2009-04-13 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- CEY Introduction - Jay Walker, 2009-04-16 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Cornell Days Welcome, 2009-04-16 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Kevin McGovern Dedication, 2009-04-16 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- K. McLane Literary Lunch, 2009-04-16 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Admitted Students of Color, 2009-04-17 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- IC Inauguration of Tom Rochon, 2009-04-17 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Alice Cook Professor Tea, 2009-04-17 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- 40th Anniversary Willard Straight Hall, 2009-04-17 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- John Cleese Professor Lecture, 2009-04-19 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Cornell Daily Sun, 2009-04-20 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- OMEA Video, 2009-04-20 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Tim Garson Introduction, 2009-04-20 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Isol Lecture, 2009-04-21 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Atkinson Dinner, 2009-04-21 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Persistent Poverty/Upward Mobility, 2009-04-22 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Office Professionals Symposium, 2009-04-22 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Kaplan Lecture Introduction, 2009-04-22 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Cook Awards Luncheon, 2009-04-23 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Prince Turki Al-Faisal, 2009-04-23 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- CAS Advisory Council, 2009-04-23 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Joint Service Clubs, 2009-04-23 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Latino Studies, 2009-04-24 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Parents Campus Visit, 2009-04-24 (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Northwestern Distinguished Alumni Award, 2009-04-25 (Box 9, Folder 41)
- International Graduate Reception, 2009-04-27 (Box 9, Folder 42)
- NSF CHESS Site Visit, 2009-04-28 (Box 9, Folder 43)
- Retiring Faculty Reception, 2009-04-29 (Box 9, Folder 44)
- Miscellaneous Projects (March/April), 2009 (Box 9, Folder 45)
- Henderson Dinner, 2009-05-01 (Box 9, Folder 46)
- WCMC-Q Commencement, 2009-05-06 (Box 9, Folder 47)
- Tower Club Dinner, 2009-05-14 (Box 9, Folder 48)
- Alumni re Financial Aid for Recruited Athletes, 2009-05-13 (Box 9, Folder 49)
- Distinguished Faculty Reception, 2009-05-18 (Box 9, Folder 50)
- Merrill Scholars, 2009-05-20 (Box 9, Folder 51)
- Advance Full Professor Retreat, 2009-05-20 (Box 9, Folder 52)
- Senior Class Campaign, 2009-05-22 (Box 9, Folder 53)
- Senior Convocation, 2009-05-23 (Box 9, Folder 54)
- PhD Ceremony, 2009-05-23 (Box 9, Folder 55)
- Faculty Awards Dinner with Trustees, 2009-05-23 (Box 9, Folder 56)
- Commencement, 2009-05-24 (Box 9, Folder 57)
- Cornell Alumni Magazine, 2009-06-01 (Box 9, Folder 58)
- Cornell Global Forum, 2009-06-01 (Box 9, Folder 59)
- WCMC Commencement, 2009-06-02 (Box 9, Folder 60)
- B. Vanneman 100th Birthday, 2009-06-04 (Box 9, Folder 61)
- CNAAA Iroquois Social, 2009-06-06 (Box 9, Folder 62)
- Reunion - 1934, 1939 and 1944, 2009-06 (Box 9, Folder 63)
- Reunion 1974, 2009-06 (Box 9, Folder 64)
- Reunion 1979, 2009-06 (Box 9, Folder 65)
- Reunion 1954, 2009-06 (Box 9, Folder 66)
- Reunion 1964, 2009-06 (Box 9, Folder 67)
- Reunion 1949, 2009-06 (Box 9, Folder 68)
- Reunion 1984, 2009-06 (Box 9, Folder 69)
- Reunion 1959, 2009-06 (Box 9, Folder 70)
- Reunion Olin Lecture, 2009-06 (Box 9, Folder 71)
- Reunion State of University Address, 2009-06 (Box 9, Folder 72)
- Staff Farwell recognition, 2009-06-08 (Box 9, Folder 73)
- Staff Graduation reception, 2009-06-08 (Box 9, Folder 74)
- BHEF Summer Meeting, 2009-06-09 (Box 9, Folder 75)
- Commencement Usher Reception, 2009-06-22 (Box 9, Folder 76)
- Biofuels Lab, 2009-06-23 (Box 9, Folder 77)
- Grounds Thank You, 2009-06-24 (Box 9, Folder 78)
- RPI STEM Dialogue, 2009-06-25 (Box 9, Folder 79)
- Ag Business Executive Education Initiative, 2009-06-25 (Box 9, Folder 80)
- NYSTF University Industry TF, 2009-06-25 (Box 9, Folder 81)
- Asian/Asian American Student Issue, 2004-2009 (Box 9, Folder 82)
- President's Climate Commitment Advancing Sustainability Action Plan (ASAP), 2007-2009 (Box 9, Folder 83)
- Cayuga Medical Center (CMC) / Weill Cornell (WCMC) Alliance - March 2010, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Cornell - Haiti Project FY10, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Reimagining Cornell - Kick-off Follow-up and Related Media, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Reimagining Cornell - Budget Model Task Force Final Report (10/09), 2009 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Reimagining Cornell - Budget Model Task Force Interim Report and Task Force Summary Reports (10/09), 2009 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Reimagining Cornell - Playbook (11/09), 2009 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Reimagining Cornell - Steering Committee 1 of 3, 2009-2010 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Reimagining Cornell - Steering Committee 2 of 3, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Reimagining Cornell - Steering Committee 3 of 3, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Senior Staff Meeting Future Agenda Items, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Senior Staff Meeting 8/24/2009, 2009-08-24 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Senior Staff Meeting 9/8/2009, 2009-09-08 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Senior Staff Meeting 9/21/2009, 2009-09-21 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Senior Staff Meeting 9/29/2009, 2009-09-29 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Senior Staff Meeting 10/5/2009, 2009-10-05 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Senior Staff Meeting 10/12/2009, 2009-10-12 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Senior Staff Meeting 10/25/2009, 2009-10-25 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Senior Staff Meeting 11/23/2009, 2009-11-23 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Senior Staff Meeting 12/7/2009, 2009-12-07 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Senior Staff Meeting 12/8/2009 Joint, 2009-12-08 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Senior Staff Meeting 12/14/2009, 2009-12-14 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Senior Leadership Group 12/15/2009, 2009-12-14 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Senior Staff Meeting 12/21/2009, 2009-12-21 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Senior Staff Meeting 1/4/2010, 2010-01-04 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Senior Staff Meeting 1/11//2010, 2010-01-11 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Senior Staff Meeting 2/8/2010, 2010-02-08 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Senior Staff Meeting 3/8/2010, 2010-03-08 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Senior Staff Meeting 4/5/2010, 2010-04-05 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Senior Staff Meeting 4/26/2010, 2010-04-26 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Senior Staff Meeting 5/17/2010, 2010-05-17 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Senior Staff Meeting 6/1/2010, 2010-06-01 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Senior Staff Meeting 6/24/2010, 2010-06-24 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Strategic Planning Phase I, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  Reports
- Student Assembly Resolutions Fall, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Student Assembly Resolutions Spring 1 of 2, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Student Assembly Resolutions Spring 2 of 2, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Students of Color, 2009-2010 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  correspondence
- Task Force on Diversifying the New York State Economy through Industry-Higher Education Partnerships, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Task Force on Diversifying the New York State Economy through Industry-Higher Education Partnerships - Background EIS (Economic Impact Study), 2007 (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Task Force on Diversifying the New York State Economy through Industry-Higher Education Partnerships - Environmental Impact, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 40)
- Task Force on Diversifying the New York State Economy through Industry-Higher Education Partnerships, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Task Force on Diversifying the New York State Economy through Industry-Higher Education Partnerships - Executive Order, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Task Force on Diversifying the New York State Economy through Industry-Higher Education Partnerships - Industry Higher Education Task Force, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Task Force on Diversifying the New York State Economy through Industry-Higher Education Partnerships - Media, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Task Force on Diversifying the New York State Economy through Industry-Higher Education Partnerships - Recommendations and Input, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Task Force on Diversifying the New York State Economy through Industry-Higher Education Partnerships, 2009-06-25 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Task Force on Diversifying the New York State Economy through Industry-Higher Education Partnerships, 2009-07-22 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Task Force on Diversifying the New York State Economy through Industry-Higher Education Partnerships, 2009-07-28 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Task Force on Diversifying the New York State Economy through Industry-Higher Education Partnerships - Meeting and Public Hearing, 2009-09-15 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Task Force on Diversifying the New York State Economy through Industry-Higher Education Partnerships - Meeting and Public Hearing, 2009-10-09 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Task Force on Diversifying the New York State Economy through Industry-Higher Education Partnerships - Meeting, 2009-12-01 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Task Force on Diversifying the New York State Economy through Industry-Higher Education Partnerships - Final Report, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Task Force on Diversifying the New York State Economy through Industry-Higher Education Partnerships - Working Groups, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Task Force on Diversifying the New York State Economy through Industry-Higher Education Partnerships - Access to Capital Working Group, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Task Force on Diversifying the New York State Economy through Industry-Higher Education Partnerships - Kitchen Sink Working Group, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Task Force on Diversifying the New York State Economy through Industry-Higher Education Partnerships - State Policies and Tax Incentives Working Group, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Task Force on Diversifying the New York State Economy through Industry-Higher Education Partnerships - University Practices Working Group, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Task Force on Diversifying the New York State Economy through Industry-Higher Education Partnerships - Idea Submissions 1 of 2, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Task Force on Diversifying the New York State Economy through Industry-Higher Education Partnerships - Idea Submissions 2 of 2, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Task Force on Diversifying the New York State Economy through Industry-Higher Education Partnerships - Presidents/Chancellors Sign-on Letter, 2010-04 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- ARECIBO, 2007-2010 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Association of Public and Land Grant Universities (APLU) Africana Initiative -Advisory Group, 2009-2010 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Clinton Global Initiative, 2008-2010 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Conflicts Disclosure Task Force, 2008-2009 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Iran, 2008-2010 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Library, 2007-2010 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- President's Climate Commitment Implementation Committee, 2007-2010 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Strategic Planning, 2006-2010 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Administrative Cost Containment Final Decision, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Budget Cuts, 2009-2011 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Mental Health/Suicide 1 of 2, 2010-2011 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Mental Health/Suicide 2 of 2, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Mental Health/Suicide Bridget Proposal, 2010-2011 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Mental Health/Suicide CBS Sunday Morning 10/3/10, 2010-2011 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Mental Health/Suicide Media, 2010-2011 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Africana Initiative, 2009-07-02 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Bahir Dar Commencement, 2009-07-04 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Pre-Freshmen Students, 2009-07-23 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Football Sr Day, 2009-07-25 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Cornell Alumni Magazine, 2009-07 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Wall Street Journal Op Ed, 2009-08-10 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Alexander Foremost Benefactor, 2009-08-17 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Gannett Staff Meeting, 2009-08-19 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- New Student Convocation, 2009-08-22 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Graduate Student Orientation, 2009-08-24 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Tapestry of Possibilities, 2009-08-25 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Welcome Back Message, 2009-08-25 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Governor's Private Meeting, 2009-08-26 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- State Fair - STEM, 2009-08-27 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- CPS Now Article, 2009-09-01 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Asian/Asian American Welcome Back, 2009-09-05 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Cornell Daily Sun, 2009-09-05 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Cayuga Medical Physicians, 2009-09-08 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Presidential Councilors, 2009-09-14 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Disability Planning Meeting, 2009-09-17 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Fall AAD Kick Off Meeting, 2009-09-21 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Eclips International, 2009-09-21 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Pediatric Ground Rounds, 2009-09-22 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Community Leaders Brunch, 2009-09-26 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Auburn Prison Program, 2009-09-29 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Flora Rosa House, 2009-09-29 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Toni Morrison Intro, 2009-10-01 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- AEM Advisory Council, 2009-10-02 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Goldman Sach's Abby Cohen Thought and Leadership, 2009-10-06 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Goldman Sach's Roundtable, 2009-10-06 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Robler/Feverstein Lunch, 2009-10-07 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Advance Site Visit, 2009-10-09 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Cornell Alumni Magazine, 2009-10-01 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Address to Staff, 2009-10-12 (Box 12, Folder 34)